{
    "subject": "resource/'65_Love_Affair",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Synthpop",
    "human_readable": "The genre of '65 Love Affair is Synthpop.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9657955169677734,
            "question": "Is '65 Love Affair considered Synthpop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8486799597740173,
            "question": "What genre of music is '65 Love Affair?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.665236234664917,
            "question": "Who are the performers of '65 Love Affair?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5613460540771484,
            "question": "Can you name some characteristics of the Synthpop genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5533677339553833,
            "question": "Are there any subgenres within Synthpop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5087512135505676,
            "question": "What are some popular songs in the Synthpop genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4353732466697693,
            "question": "How has Synthpop influenced other genres of music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3724595904350281,
            "question": "What are some popular Synthpop artists?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36533236503601074,
            "question": "When was '65 Love Affair released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24274098873138428,
            "question": "What is a typical sound or instrumentation used in Synthpop music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The genre of '65 Love Affair is Synthpop.",
            "html": "dbpedia_702_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was '65 Love Affair released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_702_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular Synthpop artists?",
            "html": "dbpedia_702_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Synthpop influenced other genres of music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_702_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_702_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_702_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_702_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_702_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_702_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_702_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_702_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_702_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_702_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_702_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text discusses \"\u201865 Love Affair\" as a pop song and makes no mention of it being synthpop.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not mention that the genre of \"65 Love Affair\" is synthpop. The information provided relates to the chart performance, personal recollections, and other details about the song but does not specify its genre."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}